I like to say Roi is a maybe I can't
guarantee it COI is is a fact this is
metrics and chill where you'll learn
practical strategies to drive consistent
and predictable
[Music]
growth okay Jen welcome to metrics and
chill it's a huge like I said to you
before we hit record it is a huge honor
for me to have you on the show been
following you for a while listen to a
couple of your interviews of which you
have a lot of if people have if this is
the first time you're listening to Jen
you should go type in Jen's name into
Spotify and filter by podcast and go
listen to some especially the interview
with Devon Reed but yeah huge honor to
have you on thank you so much thank you
so much this is by far the coolest
podcast name I've have been on so he
went I can't unfortunately this is like
the one part of the podcast I can't take
any credit for this is John the great
John bonini uh I think he I I've said
this a couple times but I think the
origin story at data box is he wrote it
as like a as like a line in some copy
and then he was like got to like I got
to use this somewhere else so they found
a way to use it so that's where the best
stuff comes from absolutely okay so for
listeners today we're going to be
covering cost of an action or COI as one
of the metrics that we're talking about
and so I guess let's start here can you
break down what do you mean when you say
cost of inaction how is it measured how
do you think about it like what's the
foundation starting point before we dive
too deep yeah so let me start with this
cost of in action is a New Concept for a
lot of people particularly in sales and
marketing so I always think when it's a
New Concept it's helpful to frame it
around something we know first so most
of us in sales and marketing are
familiar with those three letters Roi or
return on investment and Roi if we break
it down to its simplest simplest
definition is by doing something you
might see a return that looks like this
if we think about cost of an action cost
of an action the way I describe it is
like by changing nothing here is the
unintended negative consequence of how
you're currently solving the problem
today so if you stand those two up
against each other Roi requires that a
human being changes buy something do
something different so that maybe you
realize a future benefit cost of in
action is totally agnostic of the
solution it's simply saying here is how
you're currently solving the problem
today and here is the negative
consequence if it's time money risk you
name it
as a result of solving the problem in
this way and so if you put those side by
side I like to say Roi is a maybe I
can't guarantee it COI is is a fact
right like this is how much it's costing
us to solve the problem the way we're
currently solving it today I love this
framing does this come into play when
you come in and work with companies do
you encourage marketing and the
executive team and whatever to think
about this and absorb like this feels
like it has the the potential to be like
what messaging or positioning is like
from originating maybe in one place like
marketing but then trying to make its
way out and impact like all these areas
of the company or does this primarily in
your mind live in sales and is something
that's like baked into the sales process
you nailed it I don't think it should
start and end in any one function like
I've seen a lot of companies who like ah
it's marketing's job to come up with
that positioning well I think anyone
who's been in a sales role knows that if
you get something thrown over the fence
to you and you weren't a part of
co-creating it often times that's where
we see organ rejection and so in my
opinion this is a collaborative effort
where you're taking voices from sales
voices from marketing voices from sales
engineering voices from your leadership
team or your founder and saying what
ultimately is the current status quo of
how most companies solve the problem we
only exist as businesses because we have
a different take on how we believe
companies should be solving for the
solution so what is that ground upon and
I think one of the missteps is we either
see companies say like sellers that's
your job go figure it out or hey it's
marketing's job go figure it out and
then we don't have a complete picture or
a complete story so to directly answer
your question I totally think this is a
cross functional effort because
everybody adds a piece to the the pie
here and how do companies do you have
like a framework or like easy steps to
determine this because it feels like
what immediately is coming to mind is
like there's probably a number of costs
to inactivity do you try and cover all
of them do you shape them into like one
big Co you know do you frame them into
like one conglomerate like cost of
inactivity like what is what is guidance
you could provide on how to put this
together and then tie it to that anti
that anti- Roi number like the negative
number that's going to come out as a
result of not taking any action yeah and
and to be clear one of the things I
always call out too is like we're not
talking about here is not inverted Roi
so it's like sometimes I'll see people
say like oh we've got cost of in action
figure out by not buying us you're going
to see 100% less leads it's like no
that's just taking Roi and flipping it
on its head so the way I always teach
this because I think this is the easiest
way to learn the concept and then you
can kind of back into a larger
organizational message is for every
person that I'm I'm teaching is they
pick a Target account that they really
want to win for the business and what I
asked them to do is start by saying what
are the organizational goals for that
account not your functional goals but
like as a company is this a company
that's trying to break into a new
vertical is this a company that's trying
to I don't know introduce a new AI
offering like what are the big things
that the CEO is talking about that's
step one step two is to say what can I
find or even if I can't find it specific
to them what do I know from other
conversations with companies with
similar goals how do most companies
typically try to solve for that problem
and then I'll create a list of current
state Alternatives now step three is
where we kind of fall down a lot which
is instead of attacking those
Alternatives I actually want to take the
opposing view why might this different
way of solving the problem that they're
currently pursuing today why might that
be attractive like companies don't
intentionally make stupid decisions they
make decisions with the best information
they have available think like your
buyer what would be a compelling reason
why someone would choose to solve them
the problem this way as they are
currently and then if you get that right
that allows you to go to the fourth and
final step which is what
information do we know that they don't
about the beliefs and assumptions they
have that are flawed not because they
are stupid not because they are wrong
not because they don't know any better
but because something environmental has
changed and so that is the key is you
cannot get to four which is like what is
that new information if you don't do one
two and three first now as a company if
you put a bunch of Sellers and marketers
and product people and sales engineers
in a room and have them all do it what
ends up happening is you start to sus
out to your earlier point a bunch of
different themes because it's very rare
a company will only have one cost of an
action story to tell but I find rather
than look at the the like macro and say
you know what could we do which feels
hard and ugly and just a meeting I'd
want to skip start at the micro and say
let me work back from the customer and
then see are there commonalities or
patterns based on certain you know
attributes about a customer that would
indicate they are more likely to be up
against this particular cost of an
action story so that's how I do it this
is really really helpful one of the
things I feel like I'm hearing you
underline is there's a lot of empathy
involved like you hit on this a couple
different ways but it sounds like
there's a tendency and maybe one area I
was going to ask you what are the main
ways companies get this wrong so I do
want to ask that but it sounds like
maybe one of the key ways you see
companies get this wrong is they don't
enter with like aathy for like there's a
there's a good reason like there's an
assumption you're trying to enter as
like there's a good reason why they're
doing this not like coming out from like
the standard maybe sales approach where
it's like what you're doing is dumb and
this is the new hot way this is like the
new you know better future way and this
should be super clear to you it's a
completely different angle to come in
and say we totally get why you're doing
this it has a lot of Pros it just
there's maybe this other part that
you're not considering yet so let's
focus it on this yes that is exact it
right and if you think about just the
dynamic of a prospect seller
conversation prospects almost always
already enter in with a defensive
posture right because nobody likes to be
sold or convinced of everything so if I
come in and then I start calling their
baby busted as hell what do I think is
going to happen in that Dynamic like I'm
not I might be right but I'm still wrong
in my delivery and so I think it's
really important to remember we don't
win favor with customers when we come in
and we say you're an idiot because where
we do in favor is we introduce new
information about what has changed and
then we allow the dynamic to be we're
both looking at this enemy and the enemy
is not you it's this thing over here so
there's like there's this really stupid
stupid way I tell a story to show that
like how you follow those four steps
that I think everyone can kind of
understand because I'm a big believer in
like analogies and related to something
human cuz even the way I describe it I
think still sounds theoretical would it
be helpful if I just like told that
story so you could see I it okay and
just bear with me because I know it
sounds silly in the beginning but let's
say like we both work for a company and
they sell a packable rain coat now the
the purpose of a packable rain coat is
so that you stay dry in the rain right
but if you think about the customers's
goals so that's step one my goal is to
stay dry if you think about step two
step two is like what are all the ways
you could solve for the problem of
staying dry so what's the most I'll just
pull you in here like what's the most
common way we as human beings if we we
look outside and it's raining what do we
grab when we want to stay dry first I
would say umbrella yes and then second I
would say a permanently wearable
raincoat just stuck to our body so
umbrella right umbrella even if I don't
know you and you don't know me odds are
you are likely to rely on an umbrella to
stay try dry so what normally happens is
we come in as salespeople and we're like
here's all the reasons umbrellas suck
right like you hold it up and it's windy
and it inverts and you look like a
there's all this surface area on you
that gets wet and so it doesn't even do
that great of a job you forget the
umbrella and people will sit there and
say you're right yep yep yep and then we
say and our raincoat is better for all
these reasons and it only costs you $100
and that's the moment when the when the
customer sits there and says okay you're
right but am I going to drop a $100 on a
raincoat that I don't really think I
need because I've got two umbrellas and
they're good enough and this is a
dynamic I saw happening in my
conversation so if you follow follow
that four-step process you get to step
three now we're thinking why do
customers prefer umbrellas well because
umbrellas are cheap right that's why
most of us buy umbrella you buy an
umbrella for like four bucks so now step
four is I have to think about what can I
teach them that shows them that using an
umbrella is actually not that cheap the
umbrella is still cheap but using isn't
so here's what I came up with first
things first I'm going to my territory
and I'm not trying to get anybody has a
heartbeat to buy an umbrella I'm
focusing my territory on who is most
likely to feel that problem probably
people in Chicago Miami Seattle right so
Step One is filter your territory by
propensity to have the problem and then
I'm going a step further and saying it's
probably the people that like live and
work in a city who maybe walk to work so
now I'm zoned in on a high propensity
audience that have that problem step two
is now I've got to frame what is the
negative consequence of using an
umbrella well think about it it like
research actually shows if you Google
this only 5% of us remember to bring
umbrellas on days it's supposed to rain
on top of that if I live in Chicago
which I do we get 119 days of rain a
year so if I live and work in downtown
Chicago and I step outside or I step
down in the lobby and I see it's pouring
out and I've got a customer dinner to go
to unless I'm part of that 5% probably
not going to just like go out in the
rain and show up like a wet rat what I'm
going to do is I'm going to hit Uber and
Uber is going to do what Uber does and
they're going to charge me four times as
much as it should cuz of surge pricing
and so if that happens four or five
times a month I'm actually paying $200 a
month to stay dry because I forget my
umbrella so it's not attacking the
umbrella it's just saying our Behavior
around using it is fundamentally flawed
so now if you hold up a $200 a month
Uber Bill versus a onetime 100 a month
pay or $100 payment for a raincoat now
the raincoat's actually the cheap option
so I know it's a silly example but like
that's how you get to that is I first
got to understand what do they why do
they prefer status quo and then I've got
to seek to understand what might they be
missing in terms of how they are um
implementing status quo okay can I I
have like a product marketing nerd
question and I want to I want to use
your uh your story analogy because I
mean hearing an important distinction
here that I think is worth calling out
which is this thing naming this you
called it earlier like an enemy or
showing like how they're actually
missing out on money and introducing
them to this alternative is not the same
as hitting on a bunch of feature and
benefits like in this analogy there is a
place for that and you like went through
that at an earlier part but that doesn't
address the yeah but why not status quo
like it's kind of easier to go back to
my thing did I not talk about in that
example I didn't talk about the rain
code at all right right and that's where
like what I want to ask you is like okay
so so here's here's this is like taking
your example on the F this is may be a
terrible example but like feature
benefit analysis like we think about a
lot right like so okay the raincoat
offers is completely wearable and covers
your entire outfit which offers you
protection from sideways rain which an
umbrella doesn't so if you take an
umbrella you're still going to show up
wet you know your pants are going to be
wet at the dinner at the business dinner
whatever and that's not good and so it
doesn't it's inadequate coverage
compared to the raincoat which is full
coverage but your point is like people
are still going to like you can go
through all the feature and benefits but
then people are still going to say I get
it I agree that like I'll stay drier
hypothetically with a raincoat but for
the five times you know a year that I
use it or whatever is it actually worth
that cost and that's where we have to
show them actually even in those five
times you're still going to save $500 if
you use it that's I mean that's exactly
it we love to talk about ourselves so
much and even when we convince ourselves
well we're still being customer Centric
about like if you wear the raincoat you
don't get wet it's not it's us Centric
because we are talking about our
solution job number one is this person
has to believe they have a problem I
would never in a million years buy a
raincoat if I don't perceive I have a
problem with how I'm solving for staying
dry today and that's the thing I screwed
this up all the time when I started
selling run to the solution and hope by
talking about the solution I could wow
them into believing they have a problem
it's totally backwards first and formost
I have to isolate how are you solving
the problem today are there flaws with
that are those flaws costly risky enough
to the point you'd warrant action and
then I can show up and be like guess
what the reason the rain Cod is awesome
is because it is packable so you don't
have to remember it like an umbrella it
fits in your bag but that's the end
point it's not the starting point if I
try to sell you on a packable raincoat
because it fits in your bag you're
you're thinking is probably like yeah
but so does an umbrella and like why
don't I just use the umbrella until you
go through that story and you realize
gosh I'm falling into this trap this is
me and by the way remember 5% of people
never forget their umbrella there's
probably a bunch of people who don't
mind frolicking in the rain like it is
not a silver bullet message but it is a
it is a message that will resonate with
the audience who feels the problem that
you solve and that's who we should be
paying attention to in my opinion where
do you think most I want to ask two
questions one is where do you think most
companies get this wrong so let's say
you know they've listened to a couple
they've like they've heard you speak hen
is a Keno speaker FYI uh they've heard
you speak at an event or like they've
read stuff on LinkedIn from you and
they're like okay everyone like we need
to focus on this when they go to roll it
out where do they get it wrong because
I'd like listeners to be aware of a
couple danger areas like one area is
coming to mind is I would imagine it
takes a bit of time and effort and work
to like come to agreement on what this
is cuz I would imagine like CEO or like
executive team probably has like one
narrative in their mind sales people who
are encountering this every day have a
different and then product team has a
completely different like one that that
is so how do you come to alignment what
do people get wrong about that and then
my second question is um wait save it
because I'll forget your second question
okay okay yeah yeah I've got limited
mental capacity I was on the verge of
forgetting my second one already because
I took too long to ask the first one so
go ahead no the first question is
awesome so there's a few things one is
coming up with all this in a vacuum and
then not testing it with customers your
customers will be able to tell you in a
heartbeat this slaps or it doesn't or
you're missing this really critical
piece or you're blaming the customer too
much here so like take advantage of that
you everybody has some happy customers
if you say listen as we work to like
refine our messaging and focus on the
right problem for the right customers
can we just run this by you and and get
your honest reaction to it some of the
best feedback you'll get are directly
from customers we just skip over asking
them so that's one two is it like you
come in you do it you put all this hard
work on it but because it's harder we
just put it on the back burner and then
we default to what's comfortable which
is like hey we released this new feature
everybody go talk about that so that's
the the most common one is number two
like we tend to not do what's hard but
what's hard works because it's hard and
nobody else does it and then number
three is we think to micro in terms of
the problem and so like I'm running into
this right now with a client where it's
like they're talking about a problem
they solve but the problem that they
solve isn't actually a true it's not ma
up to a true business objective like
we're thinking way too narrow and so it
resonates with the end user persona but
by the time you take it up to the sea
level it's like okay yeah I get that
that's if difficult for you but what
does it have to do with anything that
matters to me so we've also got to make
sure it's the right elevation of problem
when we're selling into B2B okay okay
and how many companies do you think like
you have a good sense of of the state of
sales do you think there's a healthy
appreciation for how much loss happens
to status quo or this is like under
utiliz or people just aren't doing the
right thing with it like how do you
think this relates to fixing losing
deals to status quo versus competitors
are people do you find people are like
that you consult with are like overly
fixated on competitors when maybe like
the bulk of what they're losing is to
status quo or how does that come into
play I love this question
genuinely despite the vast amount of
research the vast amount of like yelling
into the void on LinkedIn the vast
majority of people are still way too
worried about competitive losses and the
the reason for that is a lot of times no
decision or status quo losses sound a
lot like competitive like losses so it's
like you know we are too expensive great
that's not on me the salesperson that's
on our product pricing they went with
the other person because they had a
better price well if a prospect looks at
two suppliers and both of them seem to
offer the same value and you are more
expensive you've given them no other
reason to choose you like price has to
become the decision criteria and so I
think in many ways if I look back at my
own mistakes as a salesperson I would
just assume I was losing to these other
factors that were actually just really
status quo and disguise like call me
back next year um Now isn't a good time
let me socialize this and get back to
you like I still think there's a lot of
companies who don't appreciate status
quo is
destroying destroying our Pipeline and
it's the one we have the most control
over in
fixing how do you recommend company
let's say a company's listening like
okay you've convinced me they meet with
their team they come up with an enemy or
they come you know an enemy that is not
the customer and it's not the it's
insult not insulting the customers and
they are able to frame a cost of in
action and like tie it to a number and
then they start R they test it with
customers and then they start rolling
this narrative out and they get good
responses what's a way you would expect
this to show up in a measure measurable
way that like wow this was the unlock
for us would this be like reduction in
loss deals like to status quo or like
are there other ways that you would
think about it yeah so I would say
reduction in Clos uh closed LW status
clo status quo reduction in sales cycle
time so the thing that showed up for me
is I was always like dragging prospects
along with me versus when you and part
of this is also like soft skill of
making it someone else's idea like I'm
giving you the framework toal at COI but
you're the one that hits the enter
button and the magic in that is if
someone does that versus being told it
it feels like their idea and so they are
much more likely to hang up the phone
with me walk to their boss's office and
be like look at this thing I just found
and so that helped me move sales Cycles
faster the other big benefit and this is
one I just don't think we as sales
people appreciate enough is just
disqualifying faster like there are
times I've gone in with a hypothesis
around zoi and I've been wrong the
problem just was not big enough and for
whatever reason maybe it was like a good
logo or like I could see a big
opportunity size on the other side of it
I probably would have kept working on it
by knowing up front that the problem
just wasn't big enough to solve I could
confidently walk away from that deal and
that meant I wasn't working these deals
for like 6 eight months in Enterprise
only to come up with nothing on the
other side so disqualification because
the problem isn't big enough we want
that early because that will play out
late if we don't and sorry to clarify
you mean the problem isn't big enough
that you all internally have decided to
focus COI on or the pro or what you know
is the right COI is just not to that
person to the prospect a big enough
problem exactly like I might come in
with a hypothesis on the prospect's cost
of an action and then they may give me a
an input number to that that I wasn't
expecting and I'm like wait a second
that's actually not as big as I thought
I don't know that you would need to
solve for this right now this might be a
future State problem and that is good I
want no I what I don't want are nothings
and go
yeah is COI do you recommend that when
people go through this exercise should
they always I'm looking down to the
right CU my frantic scrambled notebook
as you talk is COI always like a dollar
sign on the other end is it sometimes
time is it sometimes like more
qualitative or do you recommend like no
by the time you go through this exercise
you should have like a dollar amount
that impacts Revenue if they ignore this
problem that's a great question like of
course time in a business ultimately
equates to dollars but I wouldn't sleep
over trying to get to a specific dollar
figure like I think intensifying the
pain enough is good so I'll give you an
example there's a company I work with
and one of the problems they solve for
customers is Wi-Fi reliability right and
so when they go out to their customers a
lot of their customers are companies
that have franchise models and in the
franchise model the corporate like the
company that they're selling to is the
one that is sending out it technicians
to the Fran frch locations because
franchise owners typically don't have
their own it support and so like one of
the cost of an action stories they were
telling was how much is it costing you
to send out these it people to go solve
for things that was literally like just
reset the power button and then they
come back and it wasn't really just the
cost of their time because that's kind
of built into how businesses run but it
was what that prevented them from being
able to work on so that's why we come
back to that first step in the process
which is you really got to understand
what is it the company is trying to
achieve because sometimes it's not the
direct like COI it is because we are
wasting time over here it is limiting
our ability to actually spend time over
here which is a big corporate priority
so it's like it's like an indirect CI if
that makes sense and so yeah I think
that's really important to understand
it's not always going to be a dollar
figure right so if we determine in step
one that the company's goal is this
sometimes it will be that your COI is
exactly that and you're like great we
all one to one but a lot of times it's
going to be well in order to get there
you've got to go through these three
steps and on step two here you're
blocked and that's what like this is
enabling you to do exactly like if a
Company's trying to go through a digital
transformation and they're sending dudes
out to like ons sites that don't need to
happen well that's obviously going to
make your digital transformation take a
lot longer and that's the money thing
like that's the thing they care about so
that gets back to that I think I said
was like the second problem or the third
problem which is like our elevation is
too low don't always try to go for the
direct some sometimes the indirect is
just as powerful cuz people's time costs
money yeah yeah absolutely okay this has
been amazing I have one more question
for you
yeah where are all the areas that when
this is done well I know it's not an
overnight process but where are all the
areas that when you've seen it executed
well and really humming at a company
this this should show up in an Ideal
World so obviously we talked like most
of the time about the sales process but
like it's making me think where would it
show up in like where would it show up
with BDS where would it show up on the
website like with marketing messaging
where would it show up like I'm just
thinking there's a lot like we have our
own framework on like messaging and what
we're going to include on the website
and this isn't often something COI is
not often a concept I feel like i' pick
up on on business websites so yeah like
where are all the areas that you have
seen this done well besides just the
sales process here's the big one every
freaking website loves to do an Roi
calculator right and what is the flaw
with Roi is it's massively biased we all
know Roi is largely dependent on a ton
of factors that are within without our
control with with good implementation
working with the right team like there's
so many ifs to that but we love putting
those Roi calculators on there thinking
customers are going to like do the math
and be like wow it's a million per Roi
let's buy this today doesn't work like
that on the front end said COI
calculators label the problem give
someone a way to calculate the cost of
an action and then when they hit enter
that information obviously you have to
do some sort of like Clause here that
where the information's going but not
only helps you help that customer but
then you start to build a data asset of
like what is it typically costing people
and it's doesn't require us to do a
survey it's just people filling it out
so that can be used on a website that
could be used in BD Outreach but most
importantly I think when it comes to
outbound which is something obviously I
love talking about
it gives your BD folks and sdrs
something else to talk about in an email
other than your product and I don't know
if you've downloaded like the new app
like Apple update on your phone where
it's like summarizing your text and your
emails have you done this yet no not
yeah it scares me a little bit but I use
AI a lot but I don't know why the phone
thing is like I want AI at work I don't
want it on my phone see I don't either
but I'm like I'm always thinking about
well what is this like what is this
going to do to outbound and what is this
now if look at it it just summar your
email so don't slick you think you are
if you're like the leading provider of
this and we help companies with this
problem it's going to summarize it as a
cold email and so I it's like they do
this you're like okay I have to
fundamentally think differently about
what I am writing in cold Outreach so
that I'm not pitching my solution but
rather I'm helping a customer say hm wow
I hadn't considered that problem and so
if you ask the least experienc least
trained people on the team to go figure
that out well that's why people sit here
and Shout from the rooftops like
outbound is dead and outbound doesn't
work well maybe it does work if you talk
about different things meaning Not Your
solution but the problem so I think
there's a million Avenues where it can
be used if companies just took the time
to sit down and do the hard thinking
around it's much harder to think about
that than it is to say here's our
feature and here's why it's awesome I do
I'm going to sneak in one last question
then I promise we'll we'll be done I
said the last one was the last one good
I'm glad I'm glad this isn't a this is
awesome so this makes me so I'm like I'm
I'm trying to like on the Fly Like apply
this you know a data box I'm like okay
it brings this question is there ever a
time when it makes sense for there to be
multiple cois or in other words like
matching a COI to an ICP or to like a
specific Persona like yeah it Ur like we
we find for example like companies go
through you'll see like two this is
Broad brush RS but you'll see like two
grow stages and inflection points when
they'll come to data box for exle one is
these like much smaller businesses that
for a long time juggling the D the
native dashboards in their like software
tools and having like 20 browser tabs
open and copying and pasting data into
spreadsheets and Google Slides like what
we call manual monitoring or manual
tracking or reporting like that gets by
for a while until usually something
breaks there's an inflection point where
like something falls through the cracks
or they have a typo or this is T now
gone from taking 5 minutes to taking two
hours every week so like that's F and I
would imagine we could craft a COI
around that then there's this whole
other group where like they're bigger
they've been using visualization tools
or analytics tools for a while but now
they're ready for like increased
features and function like they need
more power they need to answer more
questions and that seems like it'd be a
completely different one that would be
like cost of being able to look around
the corner and better forecast and
you're missing opportunities and like so
the two of them are quite different and
so do you see that at companies where
like they'll craft multiple cois for
personas or for those use yes what
you're talking about is starting with
the customer first and then thinking
about your messaging and as simple and
stupid as that sounds I cannot tell you
how many times I just see companies Miss
completely there this is exactly why I
say start this process by doing it with
an end of one and you will realize very
quickly by looking at let's say 30
different accounts how many different
potential COI stories that you have
because of exactly what you mentioned
different circumstances different
problem States different level of
maturity
you have this like bag of things where
you can then give sellers direction to
say here are the three circumstantial
things you want to look for like is this
a I don't know Zer million doll company
with one person in Ops and then if it's
you see this circumstance that's
different that might lead you to lead
with this one we can never be 100% sure
the goal is to be specific but bring
that hypothesis loosely held seek to be
corrected and that's how you get this
two-way dialogue so even if we're wrong
we're not just showing up being like
what are your problems and how can we
help like that's low value so yes yes
yes yes to your question okay awesome
Jad this was so much fun thank you for
breaking all this down uh can't wait to
share it with people what how can people
work with you because there's a few
different ways I think and then where
should people go to learn more about you
yeah thanks for asking Demand genen with
aj.com is my terrible website that we
were joking out before it's in the
middle of getting a refresh um the two
way that I work with companies are
either one bringing an idea like this
into a sales kickoff so lots of
companies who have sales kickoffs um
they'll bring me in to get the
organization thinking differently about
selling on COI versus selling on Roi the
second way is the really tactical jobs
to be done with sellers so it's one
thing to know what COI is it's another
thing to say how do I write a cold email
about it like how do I bring that to
life in a discovery conversation so I do
a lot of workshops with sales teams
mostly selling into mid-market and
Enterprise who are working with deal
sizes that like warrant an approach like
this so okay that's how you can find me
awesome thank you so much again for
coming on Chen thank you this is a blast
[Music]